Department of Mathematics Records UA157
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Mathematics Records
1996 -- 2005
1918 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Mathematics
School of Arts and Sciences
UA157
6.5 Linear Feet 6 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in four series: Course information and exams by term; Exams by course; Review materials; and Textbooks.
Custodial History
See also two folders out of the Liberal Arts Collection (39090011156847).
Scope and Contents
This collection is composed of course information and exams, as well as exam review materials, a textbook, and lists of textbooks.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
From the founding of the university, mathematics was a required part of the Tufts student curriculum; originally, freshmen were offered geometry, and sophomores were offered trigonometry, with upper-level electives available to upperclassmen. In 1861, under the Walker Endowment for Mathematics, the position of tutor was created, which was filled by Benjamin Graves Brown. In 1865, this position was expanded and Brown became the first endowed professor of the school, as the Walker Professor of Mathematics. By 1874, the department was a "two-man" team consisting of Brown and S.W. Sutton, the Walker Special Instructor in Mathematics.
Traditionally, the department has only offered degrees in pure mathematics, which is the study of mathematics for the sake of discovery. However in 2011, Arts and Sciences faculty had a unanimous vote to approve a new applied mathematics major to focus on real-world applications and problems, in part due to an increase of professors focusing in this area.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Academic Departments and Programs; Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material
- Course information and exams by term, 1980 -- 2008; UA157.001; 1.7 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of descriptions of mathematics course over time, as well as corresponding exam forms from these class.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation.
  - Exams and assignments, fall [binder], 1996; UA157.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Assignments and exams, spring [binder], 1997; UA157.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, fall [binder], 1997; UA157.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, spring [binder], 1998; UA157.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, fall [binder], 1998; UA157.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, spring [binder], 1999; UA157.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, fall [binder], 1999; UA157.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Exams and assignments, spring [binder], 2000; UA157.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2000; UA157.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2001; UA157.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2001; UA157.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2002; UA157.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2002; UA157.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2003; UA157.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2003; UA157.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2004; UA157.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2004; UA157.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2005; UA157.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2005; UA157.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2006; UA157.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2006; UA157.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2007; UA157.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2007; UA157.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, spring [binder], 2008; UA157.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Course information and exams, fall [binder], 2008; UA157.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Course schedules, 1980 -- 1989; UA157.001.005.00001 (Box UA157 Shared 1)
    Fall 1980-Fall 1989.
  - Course schedules, 1990 -- 1999; UA157.001.005.00002 (Box UA157 Shared 1)
    Spring 1990-Fall 1999.
  - Course schedules, 2000 -- 2008; UA157.001.005.00003 (Box UA157 Shared 1)
    Spring 2000-Fall 2008.
- Exams by course, 1993 -- 2009; 2000 -- 2008; UA157.002; 4.8 Linear Feet
  This series consists of files of exams for mathematics courses.
  This series is arranged by class number.
  - Math 4 exams 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exams 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exams 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exams 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam III, 2008; UA157.002.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final, 2006; UA157.002.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Marth 4 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final, 2004; UA157.002.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final exam, 2002; UA157.002.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final exam, 2001; UA157.002.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Math 4 final exam, 2000; UA157.002.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 1st exam, 2001; UA157.002.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam II, 2005; UA157.002.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam III, 2008; UA157.002.002.00070 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2008; UA157.002.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.002.00072 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.002.00073 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.002.00074 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.002.00075 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00076 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00077 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00078 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00079 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00080 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam, 2003; UA157.002.002.00081 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.002.00082 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam III, 2002; UA157.002.002.00083 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.002.00084 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3 Spring, 2001; UA157.002.002.00085 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00086 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00087 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final, 2008; UA157.002.002.00088 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00089 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00090 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final, 2006; UA157.002.002.00091 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.002.00092 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.002.00093 (Box 2)
  - Math 5 final, 2005; UA157.002.002.00094 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00095 (Box 2)
  - mATH 6 FINAL 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00096 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00097 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00098 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2009; UA157.002.002.00099 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00100 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam I, 2002; UA157.002.002.00101 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00102 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.002.00103 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00104 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00105 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00106 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam II, 2005; UA157.002.002.00107 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00108 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam II, 2003; UA157.002.002.00109 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00110 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.002.00111 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2008; UA157.002.002.00112 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.002.00113 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.002.00114 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00115 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00116 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00117 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3 + solutions, 2002; UA157.002.002.00118 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.002.00119 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00120 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 final, 2008; UA157.002.002.00121 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00122 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.002.00123 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 finals exam, 2005; UA157.002.002.00124 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.002.00125 (Box 2)
  - Math 6 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.002.00126 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00127 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 exam 1, 1994; UA157.002.002.00128 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 exam 1, 1993; UA157.002.002.00129 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00130 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 exam 2, 1993; UA157.002.002.00131 (Box 2)
  - Math 7 final, 2008; UA157.002.002.00132 (Box 2)
  - Math 8 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00133 (Box 2)
  - Math 8 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00134 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00135 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00136 (Box 2)
  - Exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.002.00137 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00138 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.002.00139 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00140 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00141 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.002.00142 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.002.00143 (Box 2)
  - Math 9 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00144 (Box 2)
  - Math 10MA exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00145 (Box 2)
  - Math 10MA exam 1, 1999; UA157.002.002.00146 (Box 2)
  - Math 10MA exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00147 (Box 2)
  - 10MA exam III, 2003; UA157.002.002.00148 (Box 2)
  - Math 10MA final exam, 2003; UA157.002.002.00149 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.002.00150 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.002.00151 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00152 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.002.00153 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00154 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.002.00155 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00156 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.002.00157 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00158 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.002.00159 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00160 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.002.00161 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.002.00162 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam I, 2002; UA157.002.002.00163 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00164 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.002.00165 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.002.00166 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 1 + solution, 2000; UA157.002.002.00167 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00168 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.002.00169 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00170 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.002.00171 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.002.00172 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.002.00173 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.002.00174 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.002.00175 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00176 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.002.00177 (Box 2)
  - Math II exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00178 (Box 2)
  - Math II Exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00179 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00180 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.002.00181 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.002.00182 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.002.00183 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.002.00184 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.002.00185 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.002.00186 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00187 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.002.00188 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00189 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.002.00190 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00191 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.002.00192 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00193 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.002.00194 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.002.00195 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.002.00196 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.002.00197 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.002.00198 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00199 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.002.00200 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2008; UA157.002.002.00201 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00202 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2007; UA157.002.002.00203 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2006; UA157.002.002.00204 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.002.00205 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.002.00206 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2005; UA157.002.002.00207 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final, 2004; UA157.002.002.00208 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.002.00209 (Box 2)
  - Math 11 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.002.00210 (Box 2)
  - Math 12 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00011 (Box 2)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam II, 2003; UA157.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam II, 2002; UA157.002.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00049 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00050 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00051 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2008; UA157.002.003.00052 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00054 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2006; UA157.002.003.00055 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.003.00058 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2004; UA157.002.003.00059 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.003.00060 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00061 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final, 2003; UA157.002.003.00062 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2002; UA157.002.003.00063 (Box 3)
  - Math 12 final exam, 2002; UA157.002.003.00064 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam I, 2008; UA157.002.003.00065 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2008; UA157.002.003.00066 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00067 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2007; UA157.002.003.00068 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00069 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2006; UA157.002.003.00070 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2005; UA157.002.003.00071 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam I, 2005; UA157.002.003.00072 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00073 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2004; UA157.002.003.00074 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2003; UA157.002.003.00075 (Box 3)
  - math 13 exam I, 2002; UA157.002.003.00076 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam I, 2002; UA157.002.003.00077 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00078 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam I, 2001; UA157.002.003.00079 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2001; UA157.002.003.00080 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 1, 2000; UA157.002.003.00081 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.003.00082 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam II, 2008; UA157.002.003.00083 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2008; UA157.002.003.00084 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00085 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2007; UA157.002.003.00086 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00087 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2006; UA157.002.003.00088 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00089 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2005; UA157.002.003.00090 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 ex 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00091 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2004; UA157.002.003.00092 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2003; UA157.002.003.00093 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2 and soluions, 2003; UA157.002.003.00094 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00095 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00096 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00097 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2001; UA157.002.003.00098 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00099 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 2, 2000; UA157.002.003.00100 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00101 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00102 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2007; UA157.002.003.00103 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00104 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2006; UA157.002.003.00105 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00106 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2005; UA157.002.003.00107 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00108 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2004; UA157.002.003.00109 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00110 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2003; UA157.002.003.00111 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00112 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2002; UA157.002.003.00113 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00114 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3 makeup, 2001; UA157.002.003.00115 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2001; UA157.002.003.00116 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00117 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 exam 3, 2000; UA157.002.003.00118 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2008; UA157.002.003.00119 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00120 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00121 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2006; UA157.002.003.00122 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final exam, 2006; UA157.002.003.00123 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final exam, 2005; UA157.002.003.00124 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2005; UA157.002.003.00125 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final, 2004; UA157.002.003.00126 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final exam, 2004; UA157.002.003.00127 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00128 (Box 3)
  - Math 13 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00129 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 1 fall, 2006; UA157.002.003.00130 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 1, 2002; UA157.002.003.00131 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 1 10-15-01, 2001; UA157.002.003.00132 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 3 fall, 2006; UA157.002.003.00133 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 2, 2002; UA157.002.003.00134 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 2-make-up, 2002; UA157.002.003.00135 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 exam 3 fall, 2006; UA157.002.003.00136 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 final, 2007; UA157.002.003.00137 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 final fall, 2006; UA157.002.003.00138 (Box 3)
  - Math 17 final exam, 2003; UA157.002.003.00139 (Box 3)
  - Math 18 exam 1 sp, 2007; UA157.002.003.00140 (Box 3)
  - Math 18 exam 1 sp, 2003; UA157.002.003.00141 (Box 3)